<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LionMarket</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="lion">Lion</string>
    <string name="market">Market</string>
    <string name="earthfall_desc">"When the world ends, the fight begins! In co-op shooter Earthfall, gather your friends, load"
        "your weapons and grab your portable defenses and work together as a team to battle through"
        "swarms of ferocious aliens. Complete objectives, fortify and defend holdouts and use 3D"
        "printers to create more weapons, barricades and turrets to get the job done by slaughtering"
        "the alien scum through 10 epic levels full of brutal combat and rich lore."</string>
    <string name="battlefield_desc">"Enter mankind’s greatest conflict with Battlefield™ V as the series goes back to its roots in a"
        "never-before-seen portrayal of World War 2. Take on immersive, all-out multiplayer with"
        "your squad in experiences like the vast Grand Operations and the cooperative Combined"
        "Arms, or witness human drama set against global combat in the single player War Stories."
        "As you fight in epic, unexpected locations across the globe, enjoy the richest and most"
        "immersive Battlefield yet. Never be the same."</string>
    <string name="farcry_desc">"Far Cry 3 is an open world first-person shooter set on an island unlike any other. A place"
        "where heavily armed warlords traffic in slaves. Where outsiders are hunted for ransom. And as"
        "you embark on a desperate quest to rescue your friends, you realize that the only way to"
        "escape this darkness… is to embrace it"</string>
    <string name="residentevil_desc">"A deadly virus engulfs the residents of Raccoon City in September of 1998,plunging the"
       "city into chaos as flesh eating zombies roam the streets for survivors."
        "An unparalleled adrenaline rush, gripping storyline, and unimaginable horrors await you."
        "Witness the return of Resident Evil 2."</string>
    <string name="terraria_desc">"Dig, Fight, Explore, Build: The very world is at your fingertips as you fight for survival, fortune,"
        "and glory. Will you delve deep into cavernous expanses in search of treasure and raw"
        "materials with which to craft ever-evolving gear, machinery, and aesthetics? Perhaps you will"
        "choose instead to seek out ever-greater foes to test your mettle in combat? Maybe you will"
        "decide to construct your own city to house the host of mysterious allies you may encounter"
        "along your travels?"</string>
    <string name="theforest_desc">"As the lone survivor of a passenger jet crash, you find yourself in a mysterious forest battling"
        "to stay alive against a society of cannibalistic mutants."
        "Build, explore, survive in this terrifying first person survival horror simulator."</string>
</resources>
